<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kspaceduel.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Duelo Espacial</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Rymdduell</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Космічна дуель</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSpaceDuelxx</name>
  <summary>Space Arcade Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc arcade d'espai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego recreativo espacial</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo Espacial de Arcada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vesmírna arkádová hra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Spelhallsspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Космічна аркадна гра — дуель</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSpace Arcade Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      In KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun.
      As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Al KSpaceDuel cada un dels dos possibles jugadors controla un nau espacial satèl·lit que orbita el Sol. A mesura que el joc avança, els jugadors han d'eliminar les naus espacials del contrari amb bales o mines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">No KSpaceDuel, cada um dos dois possíveis jogadores controlam uma nave espacial que orbita em torno do Sol. À medida que o jogo evolui, os jogadores têm de eliminar a nave espacial do adversário com balas ou minas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">I Rymdduell styr var och en av två möjliga spelare ett rymdskepp som kretsar kring solen. Under spelets gång måste spelarna eliminera motståndarens rymdskepp med kulor eller minor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У «Космічній дуелі» кожен з двох можливих гравців керує космічним супутником, який обертається навколо сонця. Протягом гри гравці мають намагатися знищити супутник суперника кулями та мінами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIn KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun. As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kspaceduel</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kspaceduel</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kspaceduel.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kspaceduel</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
