<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kspaceduel.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KosmicznyPojedynek</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Duelo Espacial</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑свемирски-двобој</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑svemirski-dvoboj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑свемирски-двобој</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑svemirski-dvoboj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Rymdduell</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Космічна дуель</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSpaceDuelxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <summary>Space Arcade Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc arcade d'espai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc arcade d'espai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Vesmírná arkádová hra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Space Arcade Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego recreativo espacial</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Ruimte-arcadespel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra zręcznościowa w kosmosie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo Espacial de Arcada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vesmírna arkádová hra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Свемирска аркадна игра</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Svemirska arkadna igra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Свемирска аркадна игра</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Svemirska arkadna igra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Spelhallsspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Космічна аркадна гра — дуель</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSpace Arcade Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      In KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun.
      As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Al KSpaceDuel cada un dels dos possibles jugadors controla un nau espacial satèl·lit que orbita el Sol. A mesura que el joc avança, els jugadors han d'eliminar les naus espacials del contrari amb bales o mines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Al KSpaceDuel cada un dels dos possibles jugadors controla un nau espacial satèl·lit que orbita el Sol. A mesura que el joc avança, els jugadors han d'eliminar les naus espacials del contrari amb bales o mines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">In KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun. As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">En KSpaceDuel, cada uno de los dos posibles jugadores controla una nave espacial en órbita alrededor del Sol. A medida que el juego avanza, los jugadores deben eliminar la nave espacial del oponente con disparos o con minas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">In KSpaceDuel besturen elk van de twee mogelijke spelers een satelliet ruimteschip dat om de zon draait. Als het spel voortgaat moeten spelers het ruimteschip van de tegenstander met kogels of mijnen vernietigen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">W KosmicznymPojedynku każdy z dwóch graczy steruje orbitalnym statkiem kosmicznym krążącym wokół słońca. W trakcie gry, gracze muszą pozbyć się statku przeciwnika przy użyciu pocisków lub min.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">No KSpaceDuel, cada um dos dois possíveis jogadores controlam uma nave espacial que orbita em torno do Sol. À medida que o jogo evolui, os jogadores têm de eliminar a nave espacial do adversário com balas ou minas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">У К‑свемирском-двобоју сваки од два могућа играча управља сателитским свемирским бродом у орбити сунца. Како партија одмиче, играчи покушавају да униште противнички свемирски брод мецима или минама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">U K‑svemirskom-dvoboju svaki od dva moguća igrača upravlja satelitskim svemirskim brodom u orbiti sunca. Kako partija odmiče, igrači pokušavaju da unište protivnički svemirski brod mecima ili minama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">У К‑свемирском-двобоју сваки од два могућа играча управља сателитским свемирским бродом у орбити сунца. Како партија одмиче, играчи покушавају да униште противнички свемирски брод мецима или минама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">U K‑svemirskom-dvoboju svaki od dva moguća igrača upravlja satelitskim svemirskim brodom u orbiti sunca. Kako partija odmiče, igrači pokušavaju da unište protivnički svemirski brod mecima ili minama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">I Rymdduell styr var och en av två möjliga spelare ett rymdskepp som kretsar kring solen. Under spelets gång måste spelarna eliminera motståndarens rymdskepp med kulor eller minor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У «Космічній дуелі» кожен з двох можливих гравців керує космічним супутником, який обертається навколо сонця. Протягом гри гравці мають намагатися знищити супутник суперника кулями та мінами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIn KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun. As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kspaceduel</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kspaceduel</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kspaceduel.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kspaceduel</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
